<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alexander Cote&#39;s Personal Website on Alexander Cote</title>
    <link>https://alexandercote.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alexander Cote&#39;s Personal Website on Alexander Cote</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alexandercote.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1500W Battery Charger to Power Supply Modification</title>
      <link>https://alexandercote.github.io/projects/creations/1-deltaq-battery-charger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexandercote.github.io/projects/creations/1-deltaq-battery-charger/</guid>
      <description>Modified a Delta-Q “QuiQ 1500” battery charger to become a lab power supply. Identified locations in the control loop to override the feedback to allow for a controlled voltage and current output. Designed a circuit and implemented it using proto-board to avoid control loop saturation and initial overshoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alarm Clock and Audio Amplifier</title>
      <link>https://alexandercote.github.io/projects/creations/4-alarm-clock-and-audio-amplifer-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexandercote.github.io/projects/creations/4-alarm-clock-and-audio-amplifer-/</guid>
      <description>Worked in a team of 3 to implement a music playing alarm clock using a shield on an STM32F4 microcontroller board. Features included displaying time on a 7 segment display, alarm buttons, snooze, ability to change time and volume control. Gained practice with schematic capture, circuit design and simulation (using resistors, diodes, transistors and Op-Amps), circuit prototyping on breadboards, PCB layout and routing, basic SolidWorks design for a case and writing software for a simple real time system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Controlled LED - PID Controller</title>
      <link>https://alexandercote.github.io/projects/creations/2-light-pid-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexandercote.github.io/projects/creations/2-light-pid-controller/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://alexandercote.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexandercote.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;JSON&amp;quot;]  Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stepper Motor Controller PCB</title>
      <link>https://alexandercote.github.io/projects/creations/3-stepper-motor-controler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexandercote.github.io/projects/creations/3-stepper-motor-controler/</guid>
      <description>Designed a circuit board to control the forward and reverse motion of a 6-wire stepper motor driver. Gained practice with schematic capture, PCB layout and routing using KiCad. First design used through hole components. The updated version uses surface mount devices to allow for a smaller board design.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>